[
  {
    "position": "index_0",
    "question": "1) So for your first question, we're going to have an easy one. What is RuPaul's full name?",
    "answer": "rupaul andre charles"
  },
{
    "position": "index_1",
    "question": "2) Now things are getting a little trickier! During RuPaul's Drag Race, queens are encouraged to use their charisma, uniqueness, nerve and WHAT to snatch that crown?",
    "answer": "talent"
  },
{
    "position": "index_2",
    "question": "3) We all know how much Season 10's winner, Aquaria, wanted to be RuPaul's BFF, but who is her dragmother?",
    "answer": "sharon needles"
  },
    {
    "position": "index_3",
    "question": "4) Thanks to RuPaul's shameless self-advertising You've probably had the song stuck in your head for days, so it should be a breeze completing the following lyric, \"Don't be jealous of my ______\"?",
    "answer": "boogie"
  },
    {
    "position": "index_4",
    "question": "5) Now it's time for everyone's favourite - Snatch Game! Who impersonated Judge Judy with arguably the best performance on Snatch Game EVER?",
    "answer": "bianca del rio"
  },
    {
    "position": "index_5",
    "question": "6) Who first said \"This is NOT RuPaul's Best Friend Race\"?",
    "answer": "lashauwn beyond"
  },
    {
    "position": "index_6",
    "question": "7) The library is open! Complete the phrase, \"No Tea, No Shade, No pink ________\"?",
    "answer": "lemonade"
  },
    {
    "position": "index_7",
    "question": "8) It's time for a shock elimination! During which season of All Stars did BenDeLaCreme eliminate herself?",
    "answer": "3"
  },
    {
    "position": "index_8",
    "question": "9) Know your herstory! What year was the first season of RPDR aired on TV?",
    "answer": "2009"
  },
    {
    "position": "index_9",
    "question": "10) The time has come to LIPSYNC FOR. YOUR. LIFE! Well, not really, but RuPaul's friendship is much more important. This is your final question, so make it count. Who's music has been lip-synced to the most? ",
    "answer": "rupaul"
  }
 ]